https://www.brewerfcu.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Brewer Federal Credit Union, your member owned financial institution, is committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs and to help you reach your goals. We are equally committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Federal law requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please click here to view Brewer Federal Credit Union’s Privacy Notice.
For more information regarding our Privacy Notice, please contact us at:
Telephone: 207-989-7240
General Email: memberservices@brewerfcu.org
Sign Up for Our Newsletter!
Monthly financial updates and tips, news, events, and community info delivered right to your inbox!
Email *Select list(s) to subscribe toConstant Contact Use.By submitting this form, you are consenting to receive marketing emails from: Brewer Federal Credit Union , 77 North Main Street, Brewer, ME, 04412, http://www.BrewerFCU.org. You can revoke your consent to receive emails at any time by using the SafeUnsubscribe® link, found at the bottom of every email. Emails are serviced by Constant Contact
Copyright © 2020 Brewer Federal Credit Union • 207-989-7240 •
Privacy Policy • Routing Number 211288747
Links to Third Party Sites
You are now leaving the Brewer Federal Credit Union website and entering a third-party website over which they have no control. The credit union is not responsible for the content of the alternate website and does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction
Brewer Federal Credit Union is not responsible for the content of third-party sites hyperlinked from this page, nor do they guarantee or endorse the information, recommendations, products or services offered on third-party sites. Third-party sites may have different Privacy and Security policies than Brewer Federal Credit Union. You should review the Privacy and Security policies of any third-party website before you provide personal or confidential information.
Proceed to Third Party Site
Cancel
Quick Info
77 North Main Street
Brewer, Maine
M-W 8am to 4pm
Th & Fri 8am to 5pm
Sat 8am to Noon
